Because we are choosing who's going in and out of the event.
I'm sorry.
Why are you choosing us not to go in when we have an invite?
Right, you specifically singled us out.
That's racist.
Is it because we have hijabs?
I'm happy to talk to someone else.
It is, because that's clearly, I was afraid of this.
You singled us out of everybody.
What?
Is that against Democrats?
The whole campaign?
That's very Islamophobic.
That's very racist.
I'm sorry.
Are you?
Come on through.
Thanks for being here.
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks for being here.
They're racist.
Islamophobic, obviously.
Why is the LGBT community and you're being racist?
Did they get a ticket or something?
They're disinviting us because we have hijabs on our heads.
That's why, people, this is not a democracy.
This is disgusting.
We're being tangled down.
Obviously, we're the only hijabi women.
That's kind of clear.
They're disinviting us because we have scarves on our heads.
Literally.
That's disgusting.
I thought about it.
When we have an invitation, just like everyone else, what is the problem?
By a man who's in the LGBT community too.
You're going after another group.
Why?
Can he trust you?